http://www.peppers.com/privacy-policy

Free shipping for continental U.S. orders over $69.00. Call us at 800-998-3473 for rates to Alaska, Hawaii, Puerto Rico & Canada.
Hot Sauces
Mild HeatMedium HeatHot HeatX-Hot HeatSuper Hot HeatExtractsBrowse All Hot SaucesSpiced Products
BBQ SaucesBloody Mary MixMustardCajun InjectorNuts & SnacksRubs & Dry SeasoningsSalsasKetchup, Seasonings, Mayo & OilsCoffeeHot CandyChicken Wings SaucesMarinara & MarinadesSteak, Worcestershire, Soy & Teriyaki SaucesOlives, Garlic & VegetablesJerk Sauces & SeasoningsJelly, Preserves, Peanut Butter & ChutneyDips & Bread DippersPeppers, Pickles & RelishBrowse All Spiced ProductsGift Ideas
3 Pack Gift SetsPre-Made Gift SetsGrow Your Own Peppers4 Pack Gift SetsCollege Team Hot Sauces4 Pack Gift BoxesPersonalize Your Hot SauceBrowse All Gift IdeasGift CardFeatured
Screamin' Mimi Award WinnersTexas Rib RangersHigh River SaucesMarys GourmetOle Ray BBQ SaucesOur Best SellersWhiskey WilliesHeartbreaking DawnsPeppers Own ProductsMama VincenteBrowse All Featured ProductsSpecialty
Made With BaconSauces With A Sense of HumorTop Selling Bloody Mary MixesMade With Reaper PeppersSriracha SaucesHoliday SaucesBest Selling Ghost Pepper SaucesBest Sauces For Backyard BBQSauces With CrabMake The Best WingsBest Selling Scorpion Pepper SaucesBrowse All Specialty ProductsZesty RecipesContact Us
Log In
My Account
My Cart
Search:
Search
Need Help? Call 1-800-998-FIRE (3473)
Peppers.com takes seriously the privacy of those that visit our web site. We have established this Privacy Policy to communicate what information we collect and how that information is used and safeguarded.
By accessing this website (www.peppers.com), you acknowledge the terms and conditions expressed herein. We reserve the right to change this policy at our sole discretion and without notice.
What information is collected, and why?
When a user visits our website, we collect information about the visit that does not identify the user personally. We track information such as the domain from which the user is visiting and the user's browser type. We also collect specific information regarding the user's session on our website. This includes items such as the date and time of the visit and the pages viewed.
Sometimes we ask a user to voluntarily provide personally identifiable information (PII). This information generally includes, but is not limited to, name, e-mail address, postal address, and telephone number. We request this information when the user requests one of the following:
To register to attend an on-line seminar or demonstration
To receive specific information from us such as a whitepaper or code sample
To sign up for a mailing list
To correspond with us
Or any other such activity that we deem necessary
Peppers.com does not collect any personally identifiable financial or health-related information. We do not intentionally collect information from children under the age of 13.
How is the information used?
Non-personally identifiable information (non-PII) is collected to allow us to analyze how our website is used and to improve the content and service the website provides.
Personally identifiable information is collected for analysis to improve the content of the website and the services we provide the user.
Peppers.com owns the collected information and will not sell, trade, or rent the information to others. We may use the information to continue contact with the user. This may include contact such as follow-up calls, e-mail correspondence, or mail correspondence to follow-up on the contact or to provide marketing information about promotions, new services, or important website changes. Peppers.com may share this information with its business partners for the specific purpose of a promotion or service offering.
Are "Cookies" used on the website?
"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are placed on a web user's hard drive. We may use cookies to provide you with better service. Cookies are pieces of information that a Web site transfers to your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can make the Web more useful by storing information about your preferences for a particular site. The use of cookies is an industry standard, and many major Web sites use them to provide useful features for their customers. Cookies in and of themselves do not personally identify users, although they do identify a user's computer. Most browsers are initially set to accept cookies. If you prefer, you can set your browser to refuse cookies. However, you may not be able to take full advantage of the functionality of the Peppers.com site if you do so.
How is personally identifiable information safeguarded?
Peppers.com utilizes industry standard methods and mechanisms such as firewalls, intrusion monitoring, and passwords to protect electronic information. Multiple physical security methods such as locking devices and 24 hour premise monitoring are also employed. Finally, access to PII is limited to a small number of personnel and on a need-to-know basis.
Links to other web sites
Peppers.com web site may contain links to other internet web sites. Peppers.com neither controls nor endorses external sites and is not responsible for the content of such sites. This policy does not cover the privacy policies and data collection practices of non-Peppers.com web sites.
How to opt out of correspondence
Based on the information a user has provided, Peppers.com may send e-mail correspondence to the user. Each correspondence will contain an easy means to opt out of further correspondence.
Our Hottest Peppers
Ghost Pepper
Shop Ghost Pepper Sauces
Scorpion Pepper
Shop Scorpion Sauces
Reaper Pepper
Shop Reaper Sauces
Subscribe To Our Newsletter
Signup for our newsletter to receive regular Peppers.com news, specials and promotions.
Fill out my online form.
What The Media Says
Chip globe-trots in search of new hot sauces ... thus giving him the largest collection in the world according to Chili Pepper Magazine.
First-prize winner at the Fiery Foods Show was Peppers' Georgia Peach and Vidalia Onion.
One of the best 202 things about the South. You don't have to bask in the sun to get some heat on Rehoboth Beach this summer. Just step...
Chip Hearn is a hothead. Because everyone has a different threshold for heat, Hearn uses his entire management staff as tasters.
Chip Hearn of Peppers, a retail store and hot sauce museum in Rehoboth Beach, DE, which carries 2,000 hot sauce brands.
Our guest Chip Hearn ... publisher of Peppers Catalog and heating up with the hottest sauces.
Probably the most unique store in this part of the country.
Where you can buy any hot sauce made by man.
For lovers of hot sauce, this place is heaven.
We've been talking about them all week long. Today's the day we're ready to cook with hot sauce. We've got Chip Hearn here...
Chip Hearn's hot-sauce empire peddles some 3,000 mixtures of bottled heat. More amazing is that he's sample nearly all of them.
Chip has also created a museum of hot sauces ... If you want to have a hot time in Dewey Beach, Delaware.
© 2016-2020 Peppers.com. All Rights Reserved. Rehoboth Beach, Delaware
Website hosted and maintained by Techno Goober
Log In
My Account
My Cart
Hot Sauces
Mild HeatMedium HeatHot HeatX-Hot HeatSuper Hot HeatExtractsBrowse All Hot SaucesSpiced Products
BBQ SaucesBloody Mary MixMustardCajun InjectorNuts & SnacksRubs & Dry SeasoningsSalsasKetchup, Seasonings, Mayo & OilsCoffeeHot CandyChicken Wings SaucesMarinara & MarinadesSteak, Worcestershire, Soy & Teriyaki SaucesOlives, Garlic & VegetablesJerk Sauces & SeasoningsJelly, Preserves, Peanut Butter & ChutneyDips & Bread DippersPeppers, Pickles & RelishBrowse All Spiced ProductsGift Ideas
3 Pack Gift SetsPre-Made Gift SetsGrow Your Own Peppers4 Pack Gift SetsCollege Team Hot Sauces4 Pack Gift BoxesPersonalize Your Hot SauceBrowse All Gift IdeasGift CardFeatured
Screamin' Mimi Award WinnersTexas Rib RangersHigh River SaucesMarys GourmetOle Ray BBQ SaucesOur Best SellersWhiskey WilliesHeartbreaking DawnsPeppers Own ProductsMama VincenteBrowse All Featured ProductsSpecialty
Made With BaconSauces With A Sense of HumorTop Selling Bloody Mary MixesMade With Reaper PeppersSriracha SaucesHoliday SaucesBest Selling Ghost Pepper SaucesBest Sauces For Backyard BBQSauces With CrabMake The Best WingsBest Selling Scorpion Pepper SaucesBrowse All Specialty ProductsZesty RecipesContact Us
